<content type="html" background="images/bg/bg05.jpg">
<page title="Hong Leong Flexi FD" image="images/content/pfs/side/hlb_flexifd.jpg">

<tab title="Features">
<![CDATA[

<p><strong>Earn a high FD interest every month</strong><br />

Watch your money consistently grow as you receive high FD interest every month at the prevailing 12-month FD rate.</p>

<p><br /><strong>Get more from your FD interest</strong><br />

The FD interest you receive is automatically credited into your Flexi One Account every month so you can earn extra interest on it.</p>

<p><br /><strong>Enjoy 3.25% p.a.* when your Flexi One Account transfers excess funds* to Flexi FD</strong><br />

When the balance in your Flexi One Account exceeds RM30,000, the excess amount* is transferred into your Flexi FD Account so you earn higher FD interest. (Transfers are automatic and done once monthly in multiples of RM30,000)</p>

<p><br /><strong>Make an early partial withdrawal and still earn a high FD interest on your remaining balance</strong><br />
  
Enjoy the freedom of making an early partial withdrawal on your FD anytime you like and continue to earn a high FD interest on your remaining balance. (Partial withdrawal is in multiples of RM3,000. In accordance with ABM guidelines, a penalty for premature withdrawal will be imposed only on partially withdrawn sum.)</p>

<p><strong>No Overdraft Facility is given</strong></p>

<p><strong>Other flexible features:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>The Flexi FD Account comes with a Flexi One Account so you can have the convenience of chequing and savings at high interest rates.</li>
<li>Auto-sweeping from Flexi FD to Flexi One Account when there are insufficient funds in your Flexi One Account for in-clearing cheques and standing instruction payments. (Auto-sweep is in multiples of RM3,000. A service charge of RM5 is imposed for each auto-sweep.)</li>
<li>Flexibility to make withdrawals at any of the Hong Leong Bank branches nationwide.</li>
<li>Consolidated monthly statement for easy and convenient account management. No FD receipt issued.</li>
<li>Access your account via ATM, Internet Banking and Phone Banking.</li>
<li>Placements however has to be done in home branch.</li>
</ul>

<p><br />* Terms and conditions apply.</p>

<p><br /><em>Eligible for Protection by PIDM</em></p>

]]>
    </tab>

    <tab title="Eligibility">
<![CDATA[

<ul>
<li>The Flexi FD Account and Flexi One Account are only applicable for individuals, either single or in joint names.</li>
<li>The individual must have attained the age of 18 at the point of opening the account.</li>
<li>Non-residents may open the Flexi FD and Flexi One Account</li>
<li>The minimum initial deposit is RM10,000 for opening the Flexi FD Account</li>
<li>The minimum initial deposit is RM10 for opening the Flexi One Account.</li>
</ul>

<p><em>Eligible for Protection by PIDM</em></p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>

]]>
    </tab>

    <tab title="Fees">
      <![CDATA[
<table width="100%" class="general">
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <th>No</th>
      <th width="50%" align="left">Description / Service</th>
      <th width="50%" align="left">Charges / Fees</th>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><strong>a)</strong></td>
      <td><strong>Dishonoured Cheque (Inward Return)</strong></td>
      <td>RM10 per cheque returned</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>&nbsp;</td>
      <td colspan="2">(for postdated reason only)</td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>
<br>
<table width="100%" class="general">
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <th>No</th>
      <th width="50%" align="left">Description / Service</th>
      <th width="50%" align="left">Charges / Fees</th>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><strong>b)</strong></td>
      <td><strong>Lost Fixed Deposit Receipt</strong></td>
      <td>RM5 per receipt</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>&nbsp;</td>
      <td>&nbsp;</td>
      <td>RM10 for Letter of Indemnity</td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>
<br>
<table width="100%" class="general">
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <th>No</th>
      <th width="50%">Description / Service</th>
      <th width="50%">Charges / Fees</th>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><strong>c)</strong></td>
      <td><strong>Changes to Account</strong></td>
      <td>&nbsp;</td>
    </tr>
    <tr class="table_row">
      <td>i.</td>
      <td>Change of operating mandate</td>
      <td>RM10 per account</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>ii.</td>
      <td>Addition of joint account holders</td>
      <td>RM10 per account</td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>
<br>
<table width="100%" class="general">
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <th>No</th>
      <th width="50%">Description / Service</th>
      <th width="50%">Charges / Fees</th>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td valign="top"><p><strong>d)</strong></p></td>
      <td valign="top"><p><strong>Premature withdrawal of Fixed Deposit </strong></p></td>
      <td valign="top"><ol type="i">
          <li>Fixed Deposit of 1-3 months tenure, no interest will be paid </li>
          <li>Fixed Deposit of more than 3 months tenure:
            <ul class="arrow-list">
              <li> If uplifted before completion of 3 months, no interest will be paid </li>
              <li>If uplifted after completion of 3 months, interest at 1/2 the contracted rate will be paid for each completed month</li>
            </ul>
          </li>
        </ol></td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>
<br>
<table width="100%" class="general">
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <th>No</th>
      <th width="50%">Description / Service</th>
      <th width="50%">Charges / Fees</th>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td valign="top"><strong>e)</strong></td>
      <td valign="top"><strong>Premature withdrawal of Hong Leong Earn Now Fixed Deposit </strong></td>
      <td>Early withdrawal charge : <br>
        Interest (I) x Time (T) x Rate (R), where <br>
        I = Interest paid in advance <br>
        T = Number of days from effective date to upliftment date / 365 <br>
        R = Contracted Interest Rate</td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>
<br>
<table width="100%" class="general">
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <th>No</th>
      <th width="50%">Description / Service</th>
      <th width="50%">Charges / Fees</th>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><strong>f)</strong></td>
      <td><strong>Penalty Fee </strong>&nbsp;( Premature withdrawal of a Fixed Deposit receipt before maturity or early release of earmarking amount in a Savings or Current Account ("CASA") for FD and CASA bundling promotion) </td>
      <td>&nbsp;</td>
    </tr>
    <tr class="table_row">
      <td>i.</td>
      <td><p>Prosperity FD Promotion </p>
        <ul class="arrow-list">
          <li>2 units of Tupperware FreezerMate 650ml @ RM50,000 </li>
          <li>1 unit of The Coffee Bean &amp; Tea Leaf Beverage Machine - Kaldi @ RM1,000,000 </li>
        </ul></td>
      <td><br>
        <br>
        RM30.00 per premature withdrawal <br>
        <br>
        RM750.00 per premature withdrawal<br></td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>
]]>
    </tab>
  </page>

  <page title="Hong Leong Junior FD" image="images/content/pfs/side/hlb_juniorfd.jpg">
  <description>
<![CDATA[

<p>The Hong Leong Junior Fixed Deposit comes with a Junior Savings Account and Junior Debit Card that gives you the convenience to withdraw anytime, anywhere and still earn FD interest on the remaining balance. It's exclusively tailored for parents to save for their children to enjoy HIGHER interest so that the savings can grow faster than your child to give them the head start!</p>

]]>
</description>

<tab title="Features">
  <![CDATA[

  <ul>
<li>Earn high interest for long term FD tenures ( 12, 24, 36, 48 or 60 months ).</li>
<li>Earn 2.90% p.a. interest for first RM50,000 deposit on Junior Savings Account</li>
<li>Minimum RM1,000 FD placement only.</li>
<li>Interest calculated daily and paid monthly into your Junior Savings Account</li>
<li>Flexibility to make early-partial withdrawals from your FD and still earn FD interest on remaining balance (Partial withdrawal must be in multiples of RM3,000)</li>
<li>Equipped with a passbook to track your monthly bank balances or view it online 24/7 for FREE</li>
<li>Receive quarterly statement on summary balances and activities on Junior Savings Account and Junior FD for FREE</li>
<li>Enrol for standing instruction from Junior Savings Account to Junior FD in multiples of RM1,000 to a maximum of RM5,000 to earn higher interest</li>
<li>Peace of mind than carrying cash with the issuance of Junior Debit Card and enjoy the convenience for retail spending.</li>
<li>Partial withdrawal can be done at any Hong Leong Bank branches</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Eligible for Protection by PIDM</em></p>

]]>

  </tab>

  <tab title="Eligibility">
    <![CDATA[

    <ul>
<li>Children age below 18 years</li>
<li>Application must be submitted by parents / legal guardian</li>
<li>Minimum FD placement of RM1,000 and RM1 in Junior Savings Account.</li>
<li>Subsequent FD placement in multiples of RM1,000.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Eligible for Protection by PIDM</em></p>

    ]]>
  </tab>

  <tab title="Fees" share="p0;t2"/>
</page>

<page title="Hong Leong Senior Savers Flexi FD" image="images/content/pfs/side/hlb_seniorsaversfd.jpg">
  <description>
<![CDATA[

<p>Hong Leong Senior Savers Flexi FD is a fixed deposit that is specially designed for you to enjoy higher interest rates. With only RM10,000 deposit, you will have the benefit of monthly interest, plus greater flexibility and convenience for a comfortable retirement.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

]]>
</description>

<tab title="Features">
    <![CDATA[

<p><strong>Earn high interest, credited monthly into any Hong Leong Savings or Current Account</strong></p>

<p><strong></strong><br />You will earn higher interest rate than conventional fixed deposits for the tenures of 12, 24, 36, 48 and 60 months only.</p>

<p><br />You can enjoy monthly interest that is credited into the following Hong Leong Savings or Current Account of your choice:</p>
<ul>
<li>Hong Leong Senior Savers Savings Account</li>
<li>Hong Leong Savings Account</li>
<li>Hong Leong Basic Savings Account</li>
<li>Hong Leong One Account</li>
<li>Hong Leong Current Account</li>
<li>Hong Leong Basic Current Account</li>
<li>Hong Leong SmartLink Account</li>
<li>Hong Leong Pay&amp;Save Account</li>
</ul>

<p><strong>A fixed deposit receipt will be issued for your easy account management with monthly consolidated statement.</strong></p>

<p><br /><strong>Flexibility of early partial withdrawal on fixed deposit without losing interest on remaining balance.</strong></p>

<p><br />Partial withdrawal is in multiples of RM3,000. The outstanding balances will be printed on the reverse page of FD receipt.</p>

<p><br /><strong>Convenience to withdraw your fixed deposit at any Hong Leong Bank branches nationwide.</strong></p>

<p><em>Eligible for Protection by PIDM</em></p>

]]>
  </tab>

  <tab title="Eligibility">
    <![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>For 50 years old and above, either in single or joint names.</li>
<li>Minimum RM10,000 to open the Senior Savers Flexi FD.</li>
 
<p><em>Eligible for Protection by PIDM</em></p>
]]>
 
  </tab>

  <tab title="Fees" share="p0;t2"/>
</page>
</content>