<content type="html" background="images/bg/bg09.jpg">
<page title="Property Loan" image="images/content/pfs/side/property_loan.jpg">
<![CDATA[
<h2><strong>Hong Leong Housing Loan</strong></h2>
If you are thinking of buying a house, do consider Hong Leong Housing Loan that works hard to make the most of your money.

<p><strong>Attractive Loan Package</strong>
  <br />
Our loan package is designed to help you realise your dream without the hassles. Talk to us and find out how much more about our latest promotion. </p>
<p><strong>Extra Margin for MDTA Financing  </strong>
  <br />
Mortgage Decreasing Term Assurance is a term life insurance that covers death and total permanent disability. It is an added financial protection for your family and you. With MDTA financing, you will only need to pay a slight increase on your monthly loan installment to enjoy this benefit. </p>
<p><strong>Hassle-Free Application  </strong>
  <br />
You can submit your application through any branch, or our friendly sales personnel can visit you at your home or office to assist you. </p>
<p><strong>Flexible Repayment <br />
</strong>
  Options of a term loan or a combination of term loan and overdraft facility to suit your financial needs.
</p>
<p>Payment can now be conducted via:-  </p>
<ul>
  <li>Online Banking
    Interbank GIRO (MEPS IBG)    </li>
  <li>Automated Teller Machine (ATM)    </li>
  <li>Cash Deposit Machine (CDM)    </li>
  <li>Cheque Deposit Machine (CQM)    </li>
  <li>Hong Leong Bank Branches
    Standing Instruction Facility </li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2><strong>Hong Leong MortgagePlus</strong></h2>
Hong Leong MortgagePlus links your home loan to acurrent account to give you more savings. You save more because the daily balance in your current account would automatically offset against your principal home loan account, thus reducing your daily interest charges.
<p>
  <strong>Attractive Loan Package </strong>
  <br />
Our loan packages are designed with you in mind, making it easier and more affordable for you to own a home. </p>
<p><strong>Daily Interest Calculation</strong>
  <br />
Interest is computed on daily basis and is reduced as soon as extra payment is made on daily. </p>
<p><strong>Save on Interest</strong>
  <br />
Extra deposits or savings made towards your current account help to cut interest cost. </p>
<p><strong>Pay off your loan sooner</strong>
  <br />
Trim years off on loan duration with less interest payable. </p>
<p><strong>Simplicity of managing one account</strong>
  <br />
Maximize on interest saving when you consolidate all your funds into current account linked to the loan and utilize this account for all your banking transactional needs.</p>
<p> <strong>Flexibility in repayment and withdrawal of funds          </strong>
  <br />
Make extra payments and withdraw from your current account when you need it, without having to apply or worry on unnecessary charges or penalties. </p>
<p><strong>Easy Access to Funds</strong>
  <br />
Quick access to your funds via branch, cheque book, ATM and Internet Banking from your current account. </p>
<h2><strong>Hong Leong Shop Loan</strong></h2>
<p>If you are thinking of buying a shop, do consider Hong Leong Shop Loan that works hard to make the most of your money. </p>
<p><strong>Attractive Loan Package    <br />
  </strong>
  Our loan package is designed to help you realise your dream without the hassles. Talk to us for more information on our latest promotion.

</p>
<p><strong>Extra Margin for MDTA Financing    </strong>
  <br />
Mortgage Decreasing Term Assurance is a term life insurance that covers death and total permanent disability. It is an added financial protection for your family and you. With MDTA financing, you will only need to pay a slight increase on your monthly loan installment to enjoy this benefit. </p>
<p><strong>Hassle-Free Application</strong>
  <br />
You can submit your application through any branch, or our friendly sales personnel can visit you at your home or office to assist you. </p>
<p><strong>Flexible Repayment</strong>
  <br />
  Options of a term loan or a combination of term loan and overdraft facility to suit your financial needs.

  Payment can now be conducted via:-</p>
<ul>
  <li>Online Banking
    Interbank GIRO (MEPS IBG)</li>
  <li> Automated Teller Machine (ATM)    </li>
  <li>Cash Deposit Machine (CDM)    </li>
  <li>Cheque Deposit Machine (CQM)    </li>
  <li>Hong Leong Bank Branches
    Standing Instruction Facility </li>
</ul>
]]>
</page>

<page title="Auto Loan" image="images/content/pfs/side/car_loan.jpg">
<![CDATA[
<h2><strong>Hong Leong Car Loan</strong></h2>
When it comes to buying a car, Hong Leong Bank will put you straight in the driver's seat with our hassle-free car financing.
<p><strong>Speedy Approval</strong>
  <br />
Fast approval upon submission of your application with all the necessary documents. </p>
<p><strong>Highly Competitive Rates</strong>
  <br />
Competitive rates quoted will help lighten your repayment burden. </p>
<p><strong>Worry-free Repayment</strong>
  <br />
  Convenient payment options, conducted via:
</p>
<ul>
  <li>Online Banking
  </li>
  <li>Interbank GIRO (MEPS IBG)
  </li>
  <li>Automated Teller Machine (ATM)    </li>
  <li> Cash Deposit Machine (CDM)    </li>
  <li> Cheque Deposit Machine (CDM)    </li>
  <li> Hong Leong Bank Branches    </li>
  <li> Standing Instruction facility </li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Supportive Services for Customer Convenience</strong>
  <br />
  Our insurance and road tax renewal services relief the hassle of customers having to go to Road Transport Dept (JPJ). </p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]>
</page>

<page title="Personal Loan" image="images/content/pfs/side/personal_loan.jpg">
<![CDATA[
<h2><strong>Hong Leong Personal Loan</strong> </h2>
<p>Wish you could have more cash in your hands?  </p>
<p>With Hong Leong Personal Loan you can, because the monthly installment on our loan starts from as low as RM133.33 a month. What's more, it's really easy to apply and takes only 48 hours to approve.  </p>
<p>So apply today to start enjoying extra cash instantly! </p>
<p><strong>Get our Personal Loan today to enjoy:</strong></p>
<ul>
  <li> Monthly installments as low as RM133.33*    </li>
  <li>Fast approval within 48 hours**    </li>
  <li>Flexible repayment tenure of up to 5 years</li>
  <li> Minimum income eligibility of only RM24,000 per annum    </li>
  <li>No guarantor and no collateral </li>
</ul>
<p><strong>&nbsp;Affordable Monthly Installment</strong>
<table width="587" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0">
  <col width="130" />
  <col width="67" span="5" />
  <tr>
    <td width="130"><div align="center">Loan   Amount</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">1 Year</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">2 Years</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">3 Years</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">4 Years</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">5 Years</div></td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td width="130"><div align="center">RM5,000</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM466.67</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM258.33</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM188.89</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM154.17</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM133.33</div></td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td width="130"><div align="center">RM10,000</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM933.33</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM516.67</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM377.78</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM308.33</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM266.67</div></td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td width="130"><div align="center">RM20,000</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM1,866.67</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM1,033.33</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM755.56</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM616.67</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM533.33</div></td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td width="130"><div align="center">RM50,000</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM4,666.67</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM2,583.33</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM1,888.89</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM1,541.67</div></td>
    <td width="67"><div align="center">RM1,333.33</div></td>
  </tr>
</table>
<p>Note: Interest Rate is flat 1% per month. Actual monthly installment will be rounded up to the nearest RM5.
</p>
<p>*Based on a financing tenure of 5 years for RM5,000.  </p>
<p>**48 hour loan approval is subject to terms and conditions. Other terms and conditions apply. </p>
]]>
</page>

<page title="Share Market Finance" image="images/content/pfs/side/smf.jpg">
<![CDATA[
<h2><strong>Hong Leong Share Margin Financing</strong> (SMF)</h2>

<p>Take advantage of Hong Leong   Share Margin Financing to leverage on your assets to increase your investment   power! Increase your trading limit by using cash / Fixed Deposit, quoted   shares and / or unit trusts as collateral. </p>
<p><strong>Multiply Your Investment Power</strong>
  <br />
  Up to 2.5 times trading limit
Need not sell existing investment or withdraw existing deposits .</p>
<p><strong>Collateral Accepted</strong><br />
  Cash / Fixed Deposits pledged to Hong Leong Bank
  Acceptable quoted shares on Bursa Malaysia
  Unit Trust funds managed by HLGUT
</p>
<p><strong>High Margin of Financing</strong>
  <br />
Up to 60% margin of financing </p>
<p><strong>Trading Limit</strong>
  <br />
  Up to a maximum of 2.5 times againts Cash / Fixed Deposits
Up to a maximum of 1.5 times against Shares / HLG Unit Trusts </p>
<p><strong>Reasons why you should capitalize on our SMF packages now!</strong>
  <br />
With the volatility of the stock market and not knowing when the next market boom will hit, you would need to have a ready pool of financial resources at your immediate disposal to further invest in opportunities as they roll along. </p>
<p><strong>Enhance your investment power and seize our offer now!</strong>
  Our Share Margin Financing (SMF) packages are competitively bundled to give you the best combination of financial assistance to help you leverage on your investment portfolios and make the best out of it.
</p>
<p>Below are the benefits that you can derive when you sign up with us:
  <br />
</p>
<ul>
  <li><strong> Investment Power is Multiplied</strong><br />
    SMF loan is the only facility that gives you a higher leverage to trade shares
      <br />
      <br />
  </li>
  <li><strong>Non-liquidation of Assets</strong><br />
    Client need not liquidify existing assets to raise capital for shares trading. Thus, it increases clients' holding powers
      <br />
      <br />
  </li>
  <li><strong>Flexible Repayment
    </strong><br />
    No fixed repayment is required provided there is no Margin Call. Interest on outstanding balance is capitalized on a monthly basis.
    <br />
    <br />
  </li>
  <li><strong>Cash Drawdown
    </strong><br />
  SMF loan allows you to perform a cash drawdown upon 24-hour notification <br />
  <br />
  </li>
  <li><strong>Time & Effort Savings
    </strong><br />
    Hong Leong takes care of prompt payment to remisiers & saves client the hassle of ensuring payment reaches remisier on time.
    <br />
    <br />
  </li>
  <li><strong>Extensive List of Panel Stock Broking Partners </strong></li>
</ul>
]]>
</page>
</content>