<content style="html" background="images/bg/bg03.jpg" image="images/content/bcb/side/trade.jpg">
  <page title="Trade Services">
    <description>
Hong Leong Bank Trade Services with its worldwide network of agents banks has the capability to fulfill your needs to reach the global market. Our Trade Services Centres are located strategically nationwide.
    </description>
<tab title="Main">
<![CDATA[
<p>We offer you a wide range of trade products to assist your trade activities in the following areas:  </p>
<ul>
  <li>Imports / Local Purchases    </li>
  <li>Exports / Local Sales    </li>
  <li>Services</li>
</ul>
]]>
</tab>
<tab title="Imports / Local Purchases">
  <![CDATA[
<p><b>Letter of Credit</b><br>
Our Letters of Credit (LC) offer you a secured means of paying your suppliers by
ensuring the documents you stipulate are in order before we effect payment.</p>

<p><b>Collections</b><br>
We will inform you immediately upon receipt of the shipping documents received from
your supplier for speedy delivery of your shipping documents. </p>

<p><b>Financing</b>

  <br>
  We provide various financing options for your imports / local purchases at favourable rates:</p>
<ul>
  <li>Bankers Acceptances    </li>
  <li>Onshore Foreign Currency Loans    </li>
  <li>Trust Receipt    </li>
  <li>Invoice Financing</li>
</ul>
]]>
    </tab>
    <tab title="Exports / Local Sales">
<![CDATA[

<p><b>Letter of Credit</b>
  
  <br>
  As an exporter/seller, our Trade advisors will help you avoid discrepancies and present
  LC complying shipping documents to ensure payment against your shipping
documents. </p>
<p><b>Collections</b>
  
  <br>
  As an exporter/seller, you will present your shipping documents to us for the
  collection of proceeds. We will send your shipping documents to the buyer's banker
with specific instructions as to the release of the shipping documents. </p>
<p><b>Financing</b>
  
  <br>
  We provide various financing options for your exports / local sales, both pre and post
  shipment at favourable rates:</p>
<ul>
  <li>Bankers Acceptance    </li>
  <li>Advance Against Trade - Preshipment and Postshipment    </li>
  <li> Export Credit Refinancing - Preshipment and Postshipment    </li>
  <li>Invoice Financing    </li>
  <li>Onshore Foreign Currency Loan    </li>
  <li>Foreign Bills of Exchange Purchased /  Foreign Bills of Exchange Purchased 
    (Authority to purchase)    </li>
  <li>Domestic Bills of Exchange Purchased /  Domestic Bills of Exchange Purchased 
    (Authority to purchase) </li>
</ul>      
]]>
    </tab>
    <tab title="Services">
<![CDATA[
<p><b>Bank Guarantees </b><br>
  We can issue Bank Guarantees in standard formats favouring beneficiaries such as Tenaga Nasional, Telekom Malaysia, Jabatan Imigresen and Kastam. We can also provide guarantees such as Performance Bonds, Tender Bonds, Supplier Credit Guarantees and Financial Guarantees.
</p>
<p><b>Transferable LCs</b> <br>
  If you are a trading company, we can assist you to transfer the LCs received in your favour to your suppliers either in full or in part. This will ensure that payment risks between all parties are eliminated when complying documents are presented.  </p>
<p><b>Export Credit Insurance</b> <br>
  Export Credit Insurance assists you to extend credit terms to qualified international or domestic buyers and reduce the risk of non-payment. We can arrange for the evaluation of your buyers as well as arranging to insure them against non-payment risk. For your international trade, political or economic deterioration may also result in non-payment. This risk is similarly covered under the Export Credit Insurance.
    <br>
    <br>
  With the Export Credit Insurance in place, you can now venture into markets you would not have considered previously. You can also have the access to increased working capital with our specially structured financing product against payment of an arrangement fee. </p>

]]>
    </tab>
  </page>
</content>
