<content type="html" background="images/bg/bg2.jpg" image="images/content/about/side/priority.jpg">
<page title="Priority Banking Account">
<tab title="Main"><![CDATA[
	<p>Expect an exclusive experience with Hong Leong Priority Banking, where your total banking and transaction needs will be managed by a dedicated Relationship Manager, and a team of Product Specialists and Customer Service Executives.</p>
<p>Hong Leong Priority Banking promises you a new level of banking to meet your priorities in life, make your financial goals attainable and help enhance your lifestyle.</p>
<p>Your exclusive Priority Banking membership goes beyond the way you bank and into the way you live, with unique lifestyle benefits such as luxurious accommodation offers, dining privileges, SPA/gym and golfing privileges, and more. </p>
<p>Key Features and Benefits:</p>
<ul>
  <li>Access money easily with ATMs 24/7<br>
    </li>
  <li>Get your ATM card immediately when opening account<br>
    </li>
  <li>Earn interest on daily balances<br>
    </li>
  <li>Overdraft facility is offered upon arrangement<br>
    </li>
  <li>One cheque book free per month with 25 cheques<br>
    </li>
  <li>Free monthly statement</li>
</ul>
<p>Eligibility:</p>
<ul>
  <li>You must be 18 years old or above<br>
    </li>
  <li>Minimum initial Deposit is USD 50,000<br>
    </li>
  <li>Minimum balance requirement is USD 25,000<br>
    </li>
  <li>This account is available to individual or joint account holders.</li>
</ul>
<p>Document requirements for account opening:</p>
<ul>
  <li>Primary document:<br>
    <ul>
      <li>Cambodia National Identification Card; or<br>
      </li>
      <li>Passport<br>
      </li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li>Any two of the below secondary documents in case the primary document is not available:<br>
    <ul>
      <li>Birth certificate<br>
      </li>
      <li>Resident book<br>
      </li>
      <li>Marriage certificate<br>
      </li>
      <li>Residential Certificate by an official authority<br>
      </li>
      <li>Family book with photo of head of family<br>
      </li>
      <li>Driving license issued by an official authority </li>
    </ul>
  </li>
</ul>
<p>One of the above secondary documents must have a holder’s photograph e.g driving license and Birth certificate.</p>

]]>
	</tab>
</page>
</content>