<content type="html" background="images/bg/bg2.jpg" image="images/content/about/side/consumer_lending.jpg">
<page title="Consumer Lending">
  <description><![CDATA[
Helping you achieve your personal goals
]]>
</description>

<tab title="Main"><![CDATA[

<p>Hong Leong Bank Consumer Lending offers a variety of products to meet personal requirements, with a competitive promotion rate: </p>
<ul>
  <li>Residential Home Loan<br />
  </li>
  <li>Home Investment Loan<br />
  </li>
  <li>Home Equity Loan <br />
  </li>
  <li>Commercial Property Loan </li>
</ul>
<h3><b>Residential Home Loan</b></h3>
<p><br />
  If you are thinking of buying a house for living, do consider a Hong Leong Housing Loan that works hard to make the most of your money. And it’s designed to make life easier for you.<br />
You are able to purchase an under construction or completed residential house, to refinance your housing loan from another financial institution, and to purchase vacant residential land.</p>
<p><br />
Features and Benefits:</p>
<ul>
  <li>Loan amount may be up​ to 70% of the property value (land and building), vacant Residential land up to 50% of the property value. <br />
  </li>
  <li>Loan tenor up to 20 years, which means the monthly payment is lower than many other banks’ requirements<br />
  </li>
  <li>Promotional interest rates helps you to save on the interest payment every month<br />
  </li>
</ul>
<h3>Home Investment Loan </h3>
<p><br />
  Buying or building an investment house is a great way to build your wealth; Hong Leong Bank can assist you to reach your goal. We have specialist relationship managers to assist you in applying for your loan and getting your money faster.<br />
  <br />
Key features and benefits:</p>
<ul>
  <li>Loan amount may be up to 70% of your property value (land and building)<br />
  </li>
  <li>Loan tenor up to 20 years, which means the monthly payment is lower than many other banks’ requirements<br />
  </li>
  <li>Promotional interest rates help you to save on the interest payment every month.<br />
  </li>
</ul>
<p><b>Home equity Loan</b></p>
<p><br />
  Hong Leong Bank Home Equity Loan will help you improve your daily life, which means your loan can be used for many purposes including renovation or upgrading of your existing property, or personal consumption needs (car, education, medical treatment, etc.)<br />
</p>
<p>Key Features and benefits<br />
</p>
<ul>
  <li>Loan amount may be up to 70% of your property value (land and building)<br />
  </li>
  <li>Loan tenor up to 10 years which means the monthly payment is lower than many other bank’s requirements<br />
  </li>
  <li>Promotional interest rates help you to save on the interest payment every month<br />
  </li>
</ul>
<h3>Commercial Property Loan</h3>
<p><br />
It is designed for individual customers who wish to buy a commercial property or shop-house for their own use or for investment purposes, or refinance their commercial property loan from another financial institution. <br />
<br />
Key Feature and Benefits</p>
<ul>
  <li>Loan amount may be up to 70% of your property value (land and building)<br />
    </li>
  <li>Loan tenor up to 10 years which means the monthly payment is lower than many other bank’s requirements <br />
    </li>
  <li>Promotional interest rates help you to save on the interest payment every month.</li>
</ul>


]]>
</tab>

</page>
</content>