<content style="html" background="images/bg/bg07.jpg" image="images/content/bcb/side/cash_management.jpg">
  <page title="Cash Management">
    <description>
<![CDATA[
Hong Leong Online Business (HLOB) offers corporate customers secured online business banking and convenience via internet. This service allows customers to access real time information&apos;s and managed their cash flows at their office or while they&apos;re on the go.
Hong Leong Online Business (HLOB) is user friendly, available 7 days a week with secured encryption technology. We offer you <b>Simple, Secure and Time Saving</b> online banking.
]]>      
    </description>
<tab title="Services &amp; Features">
  <![CDATA[
<p><b>1. (a) e-Inquiry</b> 
  <br>
  e-Inquiry allows you to access your company's latest account information online for:  </p>
<ul>
  <li>Business Current Account Activity</li>
  <li>Fixed Deposits    </li>
  <li>Loans Balances    </li>
  <li>Cheques Status    </li>
  <li>Current Account Statements    </li>
  <li>Forex Rates    </li>
  <li>Money Market Rates </li>
</ul>
<p><b>1-b e-Trade Inquiry</b>
  <br>
  e-Trade Inquiry allows you to access your latest trade transactions and facilities details online for:  </p>
<ul>
  <li>Trade Facilities  </li>
  <li>Trade Product Outstanding    </li>
  <li>Trade Transactions History</li>
</ul>
<p> <b>2. e-Payments</b>
  
  <br>
  In addition to the e-Inquiry facility, e-Payments allows you to perform payment transactions online for:  </p>
<ul>
  <li>Single Payment (Intra and IBG)    </li>
  <li>Payroll (Intrabank and IBG)    </li>
  <li>Bulk Payment (for vendor and supplier)    </li>
  <li>RENTAS    </li>
  <li>Foreign TT    </li>
  <li>Bill Payment    </li>
  <li>Loan Repayment    </li>
  <li>eShare    </li>
  <li>Statutory Payment (EPF, SOCSO and IRB)    </li>
  <li>Lembaga Tabung Haji (LTH)    </li>
  <li>eDividend    </li>
  <li>Cheque Book Request    </li>
  <li>Stop Cheque Requests    </li>
  <li>e-Procurement </li>
</ul>
<p><b>3. e-Collection</b>
  
  <br>
  Hong Leong Bank will collect your regular receivables based on your instruction by debiting the buyers' accounts maintained with Hong Leong Bank or other banks. Collection transaction details will be provided to ease your company's account reconciliations.  </p>
<ul>
  <li>Direct Debit    </li>
  <li>MEPS Direct Debit <b></B></li>
</ul>
<p><b>4. Liquidity Management</B>
  
  <br>
  Auto sweep facility provides you with a convenient way in managing your daily account balances.  </p>
<ul>
  <li>Auto Sweep</li>
</ul>

]]>
    </tab>
    <tab title="Benefits">
<![CDATA[
<p><b>Ease of Use</b>
  
  <br>
  A user-friendly system with intuitive layout and simple functionality. A comprehensive User Guide is also available for customer to download for their assistance. </p>
<p><b>Real Time Access</b>
  
  <br>
  Customers are able to check their account balances real time from anywhere and anytime. </p>
<p><b>Safe and Secure</b>
  
  <br>
  Hong Leong Online Business (HLOB) with its multi layered security architecture provides you with a safe and secure environment for carrying out your daily transactions </p>
<p><b>Convenience</b>
  
  <br>
  Customers are able to perform their banking transactions from their desk and no queuing up in branches. </p>
<p><b>Comprehensive functionality</b>  <br>
Able to view account balances and perform transactions online, this saves your time and reduce paperwork. </p>

]]>
    </tab>
    <tab title="How to apply">
<![CDATA[
<p><b>How to Apply?</b> 
  
  <br>
  In just 3 easy steps, you will be able to start using Hong Leong Cash Management:  </p>
<ul>
  <li><b>Step 1</b> <br>
    Visit www.hlb.com.my to download the application form and a sample of supporting documents<br>
    <br>
  </li>
  <li><b>Step 2</b> <br>
    Complete the form and prepare the relevant supporting documents to be submitted <br>
    <br>
  </li>
  <li><b>Step 3</b> <br>
  Submit your application together with the supporting documents to your preferred HLBB/HLISB branch </li>
</ul>
<p>For more information do contact our Cash Management team: </p>
<ul>
  <li>03-2169 2683 </li>
  <li> 03-2773 0511 </li>
  <li>cmp@hlbb.hongleong.com.my </li>
</ul>
]]>
</tab>
<tab title="Contact Us">
<![CDATA[
<p>For any inquiries, please contact our designated officers at 03-2773 0511 or 03-2773 0200 during office hours or e-mail us at cmp@hlbb.hongleong.com.my  </p>
<p>Alternatively, you can walk-in to any of our branches too. </p>
]]>
</tab>
  </page>
</content>
