<content style="html" background="images/bg/bg07.jpg">
<page title="HLe Broking" image="images/content/connect/side/ebroking.jpg">
<description><![CDATA[
HLeBroking allows you the flexibility of placing your orders either through a phone call to our trading hub or via the internet. Our professional dealers centralized in the hub are always on hand to execute your transactions and monitor your shares investment portfolio. If you prefer to trade on your own, you may do so in the privacy of your office or home.
]]>
</description>

<tab title="Features"><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Free Sign-up &amp; Zero Moving Cost</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>The CDS account opening fee of RM10 and transfer fee of RM10 per counter are waived</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Lower Rates, Higher Profits</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Enjoy brokerage rates from as low as 0.10% and a minimum brokerage of RM8!</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Trading Facility</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Trading multiple up to 2x cash and share collateral at the discretion of Hong Leong Bank</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>High Interest</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Earn high interest on your credit balance subject to a minimum balance of RM1,000</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Mobile Trading</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>iPhone, iPad, Android smartphones &amp; Blackberry</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Online Cash Withdrawal</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Convenience of cash withdrawal via online</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Direct CDS Account</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Option to open Direct CDS account</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Investment Tools</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>HLeChart - our realtime charting tool provides comprehensive market analysis</li>
<li>EquitiesTracker - acquire extensive market insights, analysis and tracking by the independent equities research portal</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Portfolio &amp; Client Management System</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Access your current trading position</li>
<li>View your historical trading transactions</li>
<li>Monitor your outstanding position at your convenience</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Invest in more than just shares</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Access to futures and options market</li>
<li>Able to trade futures and options if your derivative account is activated</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Foreign Share Trading</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>6 countries - Singapore , Hong Kong , United Kingdom , United States , Australia and Thailand .</li>
<li>Foreign Online Trading available for selected countries.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>View Real Time Stock Information in our Bank Branches or the convenience of your home/office</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Available at selected HLBB branches</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Settlement Convenience through Customer's Account with us</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>On settlement date, money will be auto-debited from Hong Leong Investment Bank "Trust Account" identified by your client code</li>
<li>Sale of the shares and dividend payouts will be auto-credited to Hong Leong Investment Bank "Trust Account" identified by your client code</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Research Information Available</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>To provide research information and chart analysis from our research department so that investors can make a sound decision in their investments</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Access to News powered by Dow Jones</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Regional financial news via Dow Jones</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Professional and Friendly Services from our Dealers</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>To assist on trade transactions &amp; enquiries</li>
<li>To facilitate fast, accurate and timely execution of orders, especially for working people who are unable to monitor their portfolio via the internet</li>
</ul>
	]]>
	</tab>

	<tab title="Eligibility"><![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>You must be 18 years of age and above</li>
<li>You must not be an undischarged bankrupt</li>
<li>You must have a Hong Leong Savings or Current account</li>
<li>This account is only applicable to individuals and companies</li>
</ul>
		]]>
	</tab>

	<tab title="Start-Up Guide"><![CDATA[
<ol>
  <li><strong>Contact us for application form</strong>
    (please refer 'tables' folder under hle_broking.html for th info)
    
      <br>
      <br>
  </li>
  <li><strong>Sign up form</strong>  
    <ul>
      <li>Complete and sign up all relevant forms</li>
      <li>Send all the hardcopy forms to your preferred hub. Please find our addresses in Contact Us<br>
        <br>
      </li>
    </ul>
    </li>
  <li><strong>HLeBroking Online Trading</strong>  
    <ul>
      <li>Need online trading? Put in your preferred ID in the "Application For Opening of HLeBroking Trading Account" form (2nd page)</li>
      <li>Once your account is opened, an email will be sent to you to change password for your Online ID activation</li>
      <li>Click www.hongleongconnect.my and logon via HLeBroking login button</li>
      <li>User guide will be available in the system after login<br>
        <br>
      </li>
    </ul>
    </li>
  <li><strong>If you are an existing client and would like have ID for Online Trading</strong>
    <ul>
      <li>Firstly, please get ready your client code &amp; CDS account number. You may refer to your hub dealer or call our helpdesk 1300 88 8822 for details.</li>
      <li>Please click "Create ID" beside the HLeBroking Login button,</li>
      <li>Follow the ID Creation Guide.</li>
      <li>Please remember to print out the "Application For access To &amp; Use of HLeBroking For Securities Trading" form and send to us. Please find our addresses in "Contact Us" tab.</li>
      <li>Need to reprint the above form, please click here.</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
</ol>
		]]>
	</tab>

	<tab title="Contact Us"><![CDATA[
<p>Currently we have 6 hubs located in the various regions to provide the convenience to our customers.</p>
<p>
<strong>Central Hub 1 - Kepong:</strong><br />
Address: 3rd Floor, No. 77 C &amp; D, Lot No: 58529, Jalan Kepong, 52100 Kuala Lumpur.<br />
Tel: 03- 6252 0918<br />Fax: 03- 6252 1918<br />
Email: hlebroking-kep@hlbb.hongleong.com.my</p>

<p><strong>Central Hub 2 - Puchong:</strong><br />
2nd Floor, 26 &amp; 27 Jalan Kenari 1, Bandar Puchong Jaya, 47100 Puchong Jaya, Selangor<br />
Tel: 03-6250 2788 ( Dealing ) ; 03-8070 0918 ( Marketing )<br />
Fax: 03-80701918<br />Email: hlebroking-puc@hlbb.hongleong.com.my</p>

<p><strong>Northern Hub - Penang:</strong><br />
Address: 441-G-4, Jalan Burmah, 10350 Penang<br />
Tel: 04-228 2778<br />Fax: 04-228 6778<br />
Email: hlebroking-ptk@hlbb.hongleong.com.my</p>

<p><strong>East Malaysia Hub 1 - Kuching:</strong><br />
Address: 1st Floor, No.35, Jalan Khoo Hun Yeang, 93000 Kuching, Sarawak<br />
Tel: 082-420 784<br />Fax: 082-410 784<br />
Email: hlebroking-kch@hlbb.hongleong.com.my</p>

<p><strong>East Malaysia Hub 2 - Sibu:</strong><br />
Address: No. 18 Jalan Chew Geok Lin, 96008 Sibu Sarawak<br />
Tel: 084-341 178<br />Fax: 084-340 178<br />
Email: hlebroking-cgl@hlbb.hongleong.com.my</p>

<p><strong>Southern Hub - Johor Bahru:</strong><br />
Address: 1st Floor, No. 80 Jalan Dedap 13, Taman Johor Jaya, Johor Bahru, 81100 Johor<br />
Tel: 07-353 6778<br />Fax: 07-352 5918<br />
Email: hlebroking-jb@hlbb.hongleong.com.my</p>

<p><strong>You may also call 1300-88-8826 from anywhere in Malaysia and our helpdesk will be able to assist you too.</strong></p>

<p>Alternatively, click <strong>"call me!"</strong>, we will contact you as soon as possible.</p>
		]]>
	</tab>
</page>
</content>
