<content type="html" background="images/bg/bg10.jpg">
<page title="Priority Banking" image="images/content/pfs/side/priority_banking.jpg">
<tab title="Introduction">
  <![CDATA[
<p>Experience the difference with Hong Leong Priority Banking  </p>
<p>Expect an exclusive experience with Hong Leong Priority Banking where your total banking and transactional needs will be managed by a dedicated Relationship Manager and a team of Product Specialists and Customer Service Executives.</p>
<p>Hong Leong Priority Banking promises you a new level of banking experience to meet your priorities in life, make your        
  financial goals attainable and therefore help enhance your lifestyle. </p>
]]>
</tab>

<tab title="Privileges">
<![CDATA[
<p><b>A dedicated team puts you first </b>      
  <br />
As our Priority Banking customer, you will enjoy personalised service from your dedicated Relationship Manager,       
specially assigned to attend to all of your financial needs. </p>
<p><b>No more waiting in a queue</b>        
  <br />
  As a Priority Banking customer, you will have access to Priority Banking Centres nationwide as well as "Green Lane"         
  Services at all Hong Leong Bank branches nationwide.  Banking convenience is also one call away with Priority Phone Banking at 1800-18-9000.  You may also perform banking transactions from the comfort of your home or from your mobile phone with Hong Leong Connect Online Banking        
</p>
<p><b>Designed to perfectly fit your financial needs</b>
  <br />
  From everyday banking to long-term investing, we will create a suite of financial solutions to help meet your financial needs. In managing your investment requirements, we take a comprehensive portfolio approach where       
your individual financial goals, life stages and risk appetite are all factored in. </p>
<p><b>Hong Leong Priority Banking Premium Fixed Deposit </b>      
  <br />
Hong Leong Priority Banking Premium Fixed Deposit is specially designed for you to enjoy higher interest rates  and flexibility with a minimum initial deposit of RM50,000 and subsequent minimum deposit of RM10,000 for tenures of 6, 12 and 24 months. </p>
<p><b>Priority Banking Debit Cards  <br />
</b>      
  As a Priority Banking customer, you will receive a specially designed Priority Banking Debit Card which is an ATM         
and payment card linked to your Hong leong Current or Savings Account.</p>
<p> <b>Hong Leong Visa or MasterCard Platinum Credit Cards</b> <br />
  To match your priority status, a Hong Leong Visa Signature or MasterCard Platinum Credit Card will be issued to you       
with our compliments. </p>
]]>
</tab>
</page>
</content>